<resources>
    <string name="help">
<![CDATA[
<b>Tips</b><br/><br/>
--- Having started a walk recording, you may as well switch to other applications, where you can
make photos, record video and audio in usual way. The program - working in the background - will
find and incorporate all of these into the walk. All but the text notes, which can be added into
the walk only from inside of the program.<br/>
--- While offline during a walk, point addresses can not be determined. They will be determined on
the first walk browsing with the Internet connection.<br/>
--- Use the little known Goggle maps gesture to tilt the map. Touch an area with two fingers and
drag both fingers upwards. You will like it.<br/>
--- Option "Show point\'s details" being set, the second line of the point information panel (shows up
on a point click) looks like this:<br/><font color=#ff0000>
2:15 10.234 km 6,2 km/h 55,734316° 37,427543° 184 m (+1) ±20 m 5,2 km/h 180° #34</font><br/>
Which means: walk duration, walked distance, average speed (over the last leg),
latitude, longitude, altitude (in parenthes - relative to the walk origin), claimed horizontal
localization accuracy, instantaneous velocity (reported by GPS), instantaneous velocity direction
(degrees from the North clockwise), point number (walk origin is 0). If any of these is not
determined it is omitted.<br/>
--- The whole string could not fit into the smaller devices in the vertical orientation. The
horizontal orientation might help.<br/>
--- Don\'t set time (aside from the time zone) during the walk.<br/>
--- Some devices\' camera software does not discern between the commands to make photo and to record
video. Choose the needed function inside of the camera program itself.<br/>
--- In case you have closed the walk unwittingly, you can resume it by clicking on the button with
the walk\'s number and then on the "Resume" button.<br/>
--- Press and hold a walk in the walks screen to see the walk\'s information panel. Press and hold an
artefact on the map to see the artefact in the gallery.<br/>
--- The program uninstallation does NOT remove your artefacts from the device.
--- The "Maximum possible speed" setting helps to improve localization reliability. GPS, let alone
Wi-Fi, localization sometimes leaps wildly. To filter out such leaps, the program ignores movements
with the speed greater than the value of this setting.<br/>
--- In a new place, start your first walk in some Wi-Fi enabled place, the map will be downloaded
faster and chiper then.<br/>
]]>
    </string>
</resources>
